Just packed up a real money load, and it's coming your way.
Kamyon değerli mallarla yüklendi, sana doğru geliyor.
Look for "Rodgers" on the truck's side. Don't forget my share of the deal.
Kamyonun yan taraflnda "Rodgers" yazlyor. Benim hissemi unutma.
Shit!
Kahretsin!
- Tuna on white, no crust, right? - L don't know. How is it?
- Kabuksuz beyaz ekmek arasl ton, değil mi? - Bilmem. Ton ballğI nasll?
Every day, for the last three weeks, you've come here, asking how the tuna is.
Haftalardlr her gün gelip ton ballğI nasll diye soruyorsun.
Now, it was crappy yesterday. Lt was crappy the day before.
Dün kötüydü. Ondan önceki gün kötüydü.
And guess what? lt hasn't changed.
Biliyor musun? Değişen bir şey yok.
- L'll have the tuna. - No crust?
- Ton alaylm. - Kabuksuz ekmek mi?
No crust.
Evet.
Thank you.
Teşekkür ederim.
Talk to me, Jesse. This ain't working, brother.
Yeteneğini konuştur Jesse. Bu çallşmlyor.
Lt's your fuel map. lt's got a nasty hole.
Sorun benzin otomatiğinde. Delinmiş.
- That's why you're unloading in third. - Told you.
- Onun için üçüncü viteste güç kaybediyor. - Söylemiştim.
L'd lengthen the injector pulse a millisecond. Just tune the NOS timer, you'll run nines.
Enjeksiyon oranlnl bir milisaniye artlrlrlm. Nitrojeni ayarla, 9 saniyede maksimumdasln.
What's up with this fool? Ls he sandwich-crazy?
Nesi var bu salağln? Sandviç manyağI ml bu?
- No. He ain't here for the food, dog. - Chill out. He's slinging parts for Harry.
- Haylr. Yemek için gelmiyor buraya. - Yapma. Harry'nin dükkanlnda parça taklyor.
- L know what he's slinging. - He's trying to get in Mia's pants, dog.
- Ne taktlğlnl biliyorum. - Mia'ya bir parça takmaya çallşlyor.
- What's up, guys? - How you doing, Mia?
- Ne haber çocuklar? - Nasllsln Mia?
- How you living, girl? - Hey!
- Nasllsln canlm? - Selam!
Hey, Dom. You want something to drink?
Selam Dom. Bir şey içmek ister misin?
- He's beautiful. - L like his haircut.
- Yaklşlkllymlş. - Saç modelini beğendim.
Vince!
Vince!
- What? - Can l get you anything?
- Ne var? - Bir şey istiyor musun?
You look good.
İyi görünüyorsun.
- Thanks a lot, Mia. See you tomorrow. - Sure.
- Teşekkür ederim Mia. Yarln görüşürüz. - Tabii.
- Tomorrow? - L love this part.
- Yarln ml? - Bu bölüme baylllyorum.
Try Fatburger from now on. Get yourself a Double Cheese with fries for $2.95, faggot.
Bundan sonra hamburgerciye git. Oradan 2,95 dolara çizburger allrsln ibne.
- L like the tuna here. - Bullshit. No one likes the tuna here.
- Buranln ton ballğlnl seviyorum. - Saçma. Kimse buranln tonunu sevmez.
Yeah, well, l do.
Ama ben seviyorum.
Jesus Christ, Dom! Would you get out there? l'm sick of this shit.
Aman tanrlm Dom! DIşarl bakar mlsln? Biktlm bu saçmallktan.
L'm not kidding, Dom. Get out there!
Şaka yapmlyorum Dom. DIşarl çlk da bir bak!
- What did you put in that sandwich? - That's funny.
- O sandviçin içine ne koydun? - Çok komik.
- Dom! - All right.
- Dom! - Tamam.
- Hey, man. He was in my face. - L'm in your face.
- Benimle uğraşlyordu. - Şimdi ben seninle uğraşlyorum.
Relax! Don't push it! You embarrass me!
Sakin ol! Fazla uzatma! Beni utandlrlyorsun!
Get over there!
Şu tarafa geç!
Jesse, give me the wallet.
Jesse, cüzdanl ver bana.
"Brian Earl Spilner." Sounds like a serial killer name.
"Brian Earl Spilner." Seri katil ismine benziyor.
- Ls that what you are? - No, man.
- Öyle misin? - Haylr dostum.
Don't come around here again.
Bir daha buralara gelme.
Hey, man. This is bullshit.
Hey dostum. Bu saçmallk.
- You work for Harry, right? - Yeah. l just started.
- Harry için çallşlyorsun, değil mi? - Evet. Yeni başladlm.
You were just fired.
Yeni kovuldun.
Hey, Dominic. L appreciate what you did, in a big way.
Hey Dominic. Yaptlklarlnl takdir ediyorum, hem de çok.
Dominic, l owe you.
Sana borçluyum Dominic.
Brian, you're messing with my business. When Dominic drives, he's golden.
Brian, işimi bozuyorsun. Dominic direksiyon başlnda altln değerindedir.
Kids pour in. They want everything he has. Every performance part. They pay cash!
Çocuklar akln akln buraya gelip onda olan her parçayl almak istiyor. Nakit ödüyorlar!
- What did Dominic say? - You don't want to know.
- Dominic ne dedi? - Bilmesen daha iyi.
- He wants you out of here.
- Buradan gitmeni istiyor.
- He wants me out of here? - Yes.
- Buradan gitmemi mi istiyor? - Evet.
- And what did you say to Dom? - What do you think l said?
- Peki sen Dominic'e ne dedin? - Ne dediğimi sanlyorsun?
L told him, "Good help is hard to find."
"İyi bir yardlmcl bulmak zor" dedim.
Relax.
Sakin ol.
L need NOS.
Nitrojen oksit lazlm.
- L need NOS. - No.
- Bana nitrojen lazlm. - Haylr.
My car topped out at 140 miles per hour, this morning.
Bu sabah arabam 220 kilometrede stop etti.
Amateurs don't use nitrous oxide. l've seen how you drive. You've a heavy foot.
Amatörler nitrojen kullanmaz. Seni sürerken gördüm. Gaza fazla baslyorsun.
- You'll blow yourself to pieces. - L need one of these.
- Paramparça olacaksln. - Bunlardan bir tane lazlm bana.
One of the big ones. Actually, let's make it two.
Büyüklerinden. Hatta iki tane olsa daha iyi olur.
And, Harry, l need it by tonight.
Harry, buna bu gece ihtiyaclm var.
Hold up, hold up. Look at this snowman right here, man.
Dur bir dakika. Bir dakika. Şu soluk benizliye bak dostum.
Sweet ride. What you running under there, man?
Güzel araba. Kaportanln altlnda neler var?
- Going to make me find out the hard way? - Hell, yeah.
- Kendim mi öğreneyim yani? - Evet.
You brave. You brave. They call me Hector.
Cesursun. Bana Hector derler.
L got a last name, too, but l can't pronounce it.
Bir soyadlm da var, ama telaffuz edemiyorum.
- Brian Spilner. - Typical white-boy name.
- Brian Spilner. - Tipik bir beyaz çocuk ismi.
Know what l'm saying?
Dediğimi anladln ml?
See that over there? That's mine. My baby. L ain't cutting her loose tonight.
Şunu görüyor musun? O benim. Benim bebeğim. Onu bu gece kullanmlyorum.
- Why not? - L'm going legit, homey.
- Neden? - Yasal yarlşlara gireceğim.
Trying to get on the NlRA circuit. Heard about that?
Ulusal Yarlş Derneği'ne girmek istiyorum. Duydun mu?
- Hell, yeah. - So, what's up with you, man?
- Evet. - Sen ne yaplyorsun dostum?
- L'm just waiting for Toretto. - Shit. Better get in line. This yours?
- Toretto'yu bekliyorum. - Vay. Siraya girsen iyi edersin. Bu senin mi?
- L'm standing next to it. - EDWlN: That's funny.
- Yanlnda duruyorum ya. - Çok komik.
You know, Edwin happens to know a few things.
Edwin de bir şeyler bilir.
And one of the things Edwin knows is: lt's not how you stand by your car,
Edwin'in bildiği şeylerden biri şu: Mesele, arabanln yanlnda nasll durduğun değil,
it's how you race your car. You better learn that.
onu nasll yarlştlrdlğlndlr. Bunu öğrensen iyi edersin.
Oh, shit. Here they come. lt's on.
Vay canlna. Geliyorlar. Başllyoruz.
- Dom. - Marvin.
- Dom. - Marvin.
- Hey, Dom. How you doing? - Hey, Camille. You been doing yoga?
- Selam Dom. Nasllsln? - Selam Camille. Yoga ml yaplyordun?
You did? Of course you did. Monica.
Yaptln ml? Tabii ki yaptln. Monica.
L smell skanks.
Orospu kokusu allyorum.
Why don't you girls pack it up, before l leave tread marks on your face?
Kizlar, ben yüzünüzde tekme izi blrakmadan neden çekip gitmiyorsunuz?
Okay.
Tamam.
- Letty, l was just talking. - Yeah. Whatever.
- Letty, ben sadece konuşuyordum. - Evet. Ne demezsin.
- Okay, Hector. - Yeah? What's up, man?
- Pekala, Hector. - Evet? Nasllsln dostum?
- EDWlN: Yo. What's up? - Edwin.
- Selam. Ne haber? - Edwin.
- How we doing this tonight? - One race.
- Bu gece nasll yaplyoruz? - Tek yarlş olacak.
$2,000 buy-in. Winner takes all. Hector, you're going to hold the cash.
2000 dolar koyuyoruz. Kazanan hepsini allr. Hector, para sende dursun.
- Why Hector? - Too slow to make away with the money.
- Neden Hector? - Parayla kaçamayacak kadar yavaş da ondan.
- Okay. Good luck, guys. - BRlAN: Hey, wait. Hold up.
- Tamam. İyi şanslar çocuklar. - Hey, bekle. Bir dakika.
L don't have any cash. But l do have the pink slip to my car.
Hiç nakit param yok. Ama ortaya arabaml koyuyorum.
You just can't climb in the ring with Ali, 'cause you think you box.
Sirf boks yaptlğlnl sanlyorsun diye Muhammed Ali'yle ringe çlkamazsln.
He knows l can box. Check it out. Lt's like this.
O benim boks yapabildiğimi biliyor. Benim fikrim şu:
L lose, the winner takes my car. Clean and clear.
Kaybedersem, kazanan arabaml allr. Temiz ve net.
But if l win, l take the cash, and l take the respect.
Ama kazanlrsam, para ve onur benim olur.
Respect.
Onur mu?
To some people, that's more important.
Bazl insanlar için bu daha önemlidir.
That your car?
Araban bu mu?
L see a cool air intake. lt's got a NOS fogger system and a T4 turbo, Dominic.
Soğuk hava emme sistemi görüyorum. Nitrojen karlştlrlclll T4 turbo motor var.
L see an AlC controller. Lt has direct port nitrous injection.
Ekstra enjektör regülatörü görüyorum. Direkt nitrojen enjeksiyon borusu var.
Yeah. And a stand-alone fuel management system.
Ve kendi kendine çallşan bir benzin kontrol sistemi.
Not a bad way to spend $1 0,000.
1 0.000 dolarl boşa harcamamlşsln.
EDWlN: You see that shit?
Şunu görüyor musun?
He's got enough NOS in there to blow himself up. Period.
Kendini havaya uçuracak kadar nitrojen var. Başka söze ne hacet.
- So, what do you say? Am l worthy? - We don't know yet.
- Ne diyorsun? Buna değer miyim? - Henüz bilmiyoruz.
But you're in. Let's go.
Ama yarlştasln. Gidelim.
- All right. - Let's go!
- Pekala. - Gidelim!
- What the hell is going on around here? - Street's closed, pizza boy.
- Burada neler oluyor? - Bu sokak kapall pizzacl çocuk.
- Find another way home. - Goddamn street racers.
- Evine başka yoldan git. - Kahrolasl sokak yarlşçllarl.
DlSPATCHER: Log on, 22. Code 3. Tension is high. They've blocked the street.
Acil durum. Tansiyon yüksek. Sokağı kapatmışlar.
Edwin.
Edwin.
This is yours, whether you win or lose.
Bu senin, kazansan da kaybetsen de.
But if you win, you get her, too.
Ama kazanlrsan, onu da allrsln.
You're going to win.
Kazanacaksln.
L'm going to win.
Kazanacağlm.
We had a reported homicide. 187, at Barabian Liquors.
Bir cinayet bildirildi. Barabian içki dükkanında.
L've got a 1 87 in Glendale. Cops are all over it. We're good to roll.
Glendale'de bir cinayet olmuş. Polisler bununla meşgul. Başlamaya hazlrlz.
- All right. - Let's race!
- Tamam. - Haydi yarlşallm!
Right.
Peki.
Go!
Başla!
Hell, yeah!
Haydi!
Damn, that guy's fast.
Vay be, bu herif bayağI hlzll.
Let's go! Ménage à!
Gidelim! Bekleyin klzlar!
No! Monica!
Haylr! Monica!
Shut up!
Kapa çeneni!
- Let's go now, baby! - Yeah!
- Haydi bakallm bebek! - Evet!
Come on. Come on. Back up.
Haydi. Haydi. Geri çekilin.
Here's what you won, right here. There you go.
İşte ödülün, tam burada. Al bakallm.
You were racing a bunch of skateboards. Know what l mean?
Tosbağalarla yarlşlyordun. Ne dediğimi anladln ml?
My sister holds the money. Count it.
Paralar kardeşimde. Hepsini say.
Me and my trophy.
İşte benim kupam.
- Hey, Monica. What's up, baby? - What's your problem? You didn't win.
- Selam Monica. Nasllsln bebek? - Neyin var senin? Kazanamadln ki.
Fuck you then!
Siktir!
Was that fun?
Eğlenceli miydi?
Got a problem there, buddy?
Bir sorunun mu var ahbap?
- What are you smiling about? - Dude. l almost had you.
- Niye gülüyorsun? - Neredeyse yeniyordum seni ahbap.
You almost had me?
Neredeyse beni yeniyor muydun?
You never had me. You never had your car.
Beni yenmedin. Arabana hakim olamadln.
Granny-shifting. Not double-clutching, like you should.
Vitesi anneannem gibi değiştiriyordun. Çok seri olman lazlm.
You're lucky that 1 00-shot of NOS didn't blow the welds on the intake.
1 00 birim nitrojen oksit, emme manifoldu kaynaklarlnl eritmediği için şansllsln.
- Almost had me? - You tell him, Dominic. Get out of here.
- Neredeyse beni yeniyormuş. - Haddini bildir ona. Defolsun buradan.
Now, me and the mad scientist got to rip apart the block
Şimdi bu çllgln bilim adamlyla ben motoru söküp
and replace the piston rings you fried.
yaktlğln piston segmanlarlnl değiştirmek zorundaylz.
Ask any racer. Any real racer.
İstediğin yarlşçlya sor. Gerçek yarlşçlya.
Lt don't matter if you win by an inch or a mile. Winning's winning.
Ha santim farklyla yenmişsin, ha kilometre farklyla. Kazanmak kazanmaktlr.
Yeah!
Evet!
DlSPATCHER: All available units, we have street-racing along Hawthorne....
Bütün birimlerin dikkatine, Hawthorne yakınında sokak yarışı...
Oh, shit! We got cops. Cops!
Kahretsin! Polis geliyor. Polisler!
Go!
Gidelim!
Cops! Get in the car! Go!
Polisler! Arabaya bin! Çabuk!
OFFlCER: Toretto, stop right there!
Toretto, olduğun yerde kal!
Toretto!
Toretto!
Get in!
Atla!
You're the last person in the world l expected to show up.
Karşlma çlkacağlnl düşündüğüm en son kişi sendin.
L thought if l got in your good graces, you might let me keep my car.
Minnetini kazanlrsam, arabaml bana blraklrsln diye düşündüm.
You are in my good graces, but you ain't keeping your car.
Minnetimi kazandln, ama araban sende kalmayacak.
You drive like you've done this before. Are you a wheelman?
Bunu daha önce yapmlş gibisin. Kanun kaçağI mlsln?
- No. - You boost cars?
- Haylr. - Araba ml çallyorsun?
- No. Never. - Ever done time?
- Haylr. Asla. - Hiç kodeste yattln ml?
Couple of overnighters. No big deal.
Birkaç gece gözaltl falan. Önemli değil.
What about the two years in juvie for boosting cars?
Araba hlrslzllğlndan iki yll Islahevinde kalmadln ml yani?
Tucson, right?
Tucson'da, değil mi?
L had Jesse run a profile on you, Brian Earl Spilner.
Jesse'ye hakklnda bir dosya hazlrlattlm Brian Earl Spilner.
He'll find anything on the Web. Anything about anybody.
İnternet'te her şeyi bulabilir. Herkes hakklnda her şeyi.
So, why bullshit?
Niye yalan söylüyorsun?
So, what about you?
Ya sen?
Two years in Lompoc.
Lompoc'da iki yll.
L'll die before l go back.
Oraya geri döneceğime ölürüm.
- Oh, great. - What?
- Harika. - Ne oldu?
Lt's going to be a long-ass night. That's what.
Uzun bir gece olacak. Olan bu.
Follow us.
Bizi takip et.
L thought we had an agreement. You stay away. l stay away.
Bir anlaşmamlz olduğunu sanlyordum. Sen uzak durursun. Ben uzak dururum.
Everybody stays happy.
Herkes mutlu olur.
We got lost. What do you want me to tell you?
Kaybolduk. Sana ne söylememi istiyorsun?
- Who's "we"? - My new mechanic.
- "Biz" kim? - Yeni tamircim.
Brian, meet Johnny Tran.
Brian, Johnny Tran'le tanlş.
The guy in the snakeskin pants. That's his cousin. Lance.
Yllan derisi pantolonlu adam. Bu da kuzeni Lance.
So, when are you going to give me a shot at that Honda 2000 of yours?
Ne zaman şu senin Honda 2000'e binmeme izin vereceksin?
- This your ride? - Lt was. lt's his now.
- Bu senin araban ml? - Benimdi. Şimdi onun.
No, it's not. l haven't taken delivery.
Haylr, değil. Henüz teslim almadlm.
Then, it's nobody's car. But somebody put in the wrench time.
O zaman kimsenin arabasl değil. Ama birisi onu fazla zorlamlş.
- What do you think, Lance? - Lt's an amazing machine.
- Ne düşünüyorsun Lance? - Muhteşem bir makine.
Yes, indeed.
Gerçekten öyle.
Let's go.
Gidelim.
L'll see you in the desert next month. Be ready to have your ass handed to you.
Gelecek ay çölde görüşürüz. Hazlr ol, seni ezip geçeceğim.
- You'll need more than that crotch rocket. - L got something for you.
- O motosikletten fazlaslna ihtiyacln olacak. - Senin için bir sürprizim var.
- What the hell was that all about? - Long story. l'll tell you later.
- Neydi bütün bunlar? - Uzun hikaye. Sonra anlatlrlm.
Let's get out of here.
Gidelim buradan.
NOS!
Nitrojen!
- BRlAN: So, what the hell was that all about? - Lt's a long story.
- Neydi bütün bunlar? - Uzun bir hikaye.
BRlAN: Well, we got a 20-mile hike. Humor me.
30 kilometrelik yolumuz var. Eğlendir beni.
A business deal that went sour.
Kötü sonuçlanan bir iş anlaşmasl.
Plus, l made the mistake of sleeping with his sister.
Üstüne üstlük, klz kardeşiyle yatmak gibi bir hata yaptlm.
Take care.
Dikkat et.
Yo, Spilner.
Hey, Spilner.
- You want a beer? - Yeah, sure.
- Bira ister misin? - Evet, tabii.
Oh, shit.
Kahretsin.
- You're all in, right? - Wow, man, she's hot.
- Hepiniz varslnlz, değil mi? - Vay canlna, çok seksi.
- Which one of you uses nitrous? - Yo.
- Hanginiz nitrojen kullanlyorsunuz? - Ben.
Yo, Dom. We were just about to go looking for you, brother.
Hey, Dom. Neredeyse seni aramaya çlklyorduk.
Where were you?
Neredeydin?
There were mass cops there. They came in from every direction. lt was orchestrated.
Orada sürüyle polis vardl. Her yönden geldiler. Fena bastlrdllar.
- This your beer? - Yeah, that's my beer.
- Bu senin biran ml? - Evet, benim biram.
Yo, Einstein. Take it upstairs.
Hey, Einstein. Onu üst kata çlkar.
You can't detail a car with the cover on.
Kaporta kapallyken arabayl muayene edemezsin.
- Can't even get that right. - You all right?
- Bunu bile doğru yapamlyorsun. - İyi misin sen?
- Am l all right? - Lt was just a question.
- İyi miyim? - Öylesine sordum.
Yo, Dom.
Hey, Dom.
- Why did you bring the buster here? - 'Cause he kept me out of handcuffs!
- O herifi niye buraya getirdin? - Çünkü beni kelepçelerden kurtardl!
He didn't just run back to the fort! The buster brought me back.
O sizin gibi hemen buraya kaçmadl! Bu herif beni geri getirdi.
You can have any brew you want, as long as it's a Corona.
İstediğin içkiyi alabilirsin, markasl Corona olduğu sürece.
- Thanks, man. - That's Vince's. So, enjoy it.
- Sağol dostum. - O Vince'in. Afiyet olsun.
You.
Sen.
- Hey, bro. You got a bathroom? - Upstairs. First door on the right.
- Hey, dostum. Tuvalet nerede? - Üst katta. Sağda ilk kapl.
He's got no call being up in here. You don't know that fool for shit.
Burada olmaya hakkl yok. Onu hiç tanlmlyorsun.
- He's right, Dom. - There was a time when l didn't know you.
- Hakll Dom. - Bir zamanlar seni de tanlmlyordum.
That was in the third grade!
O zaman ilkokul üçteydik!
- Yeah. So, what girls are here? - You name it. You want mine?
- Evet. Nasll klzlar var? - Seç bir tane. Benimkini ister misin?
- You need to shut the... - You want two?
- Kapat çeneni... - İki tane mi istiyorsun?
- You don't have anything? - You look a bit tired.
- Bir şeyin yok ya? - Biraz yorgun görünüyorsun.
L think you should go upstairs and give me a massage.
Bence yukarl çlklp bana masaj yapmallsln.
- Look at all our guests. - How about you give me a massage?
- Misafirlerimiz var. - Bana masaj yapmaya ne dersin?
Crazy bitch.
Çilgln kadln.
You know you owe me a 1 0-second car, right?
Bana 1 0 saniyede maksimuma çlkan bir araba borçlusun.
Oh, shit.
Kahretsin.
Did you wipe the seat?
Klozeti sildin mi?
Jesus Christ! Would you cut this shit? Come on!
Tanrl aşklna! Şunu keser misin? Haydi!
- Come on. Let's go get me a drink. - We were just about to get along.
- Haydi. Gidip bana içki alallm. - Tam da kaynaşmaya başlamlştlk.
- So, what do you want? - Anything, as long as it's cold.
- Ne istiyorsun? - Ne olursa, soğuk olsun yeter.
You know, my brother likes you. He usually doesn't like anybody.
Ağabeyim senden hoşlandl. Genellikle kimseyi sevmez.
- He's a complicated guy. - Yeah? What about you?
- Zor bir adam. - Öyle mi? Ya sen?
- L'm simpler. - You're a shitty liar.
- Ben daha basitim. - Kötü bir yalanclsln.
Well, l'll take that as a compliment.
Bunu bir iltifat olarak kabul ediyorum.
- But there's a problem. - What's that?
- Ama bir sorun var. - Nedir?
You need to get some sleep.
Biraz uyuman lazlm.
And you definitely, definitely need a shower.
Ve kesinlikle duş alman lazlm.
Come on. l'll take you home.
Haydi. Seni eve götüreyim.
OFFlCER: Show me your hands. Very good. Now open the door.
Ellerini göster bana. Çok güzel. Şimdi kapıyı aç.
Put your hands on your head. Behind your head.
Ellerini başının üstüne koy. Başının arkasına.
Face the front of the vehicle, walk backwards towards the rear.
Yüzünü arabanın önüne dön, arkaya doğru geri geri yürü.
Take two steps to your right. Stop right there.
Sağına iki adım at. Tam orada dur.
- What did l do? - Shut up. He's clean, Sarge.
- Ne yaptlm? - Kes sesini. Temiz komiserim.
Damn! Muse, will you take these things off?
Kahretsin! Şunlarl çlkarlr mlsln?
- Shit. You put them on so tight. - L like realism.
- Kahretsin. Çok slkmlşsln. - Gerçekçiliği severim.
You never know who's watching, Brian.
Kimin seyrettiğini asla bilemezsin Brian.
Nice crib, Sergeant. lt's a lot nicer than the last place you confiscated.
Güzel ev komiser. El koyduğun bir önceki yerden çok daha iyi.
Ain't it? Eddie Fisher built this house for Elizabeth Taylor in the '50s.
Değil mi? 1 950'lerde Eddie Fisher, Elizabeth Taylor için yaptlrmlş bu evi.
You see, even the cops are Hollywood in Hollywood.
Hollywood'da polisler bile Hollywood'laşlyor.
Okay, here he is, fresh from Toretto's hot rod heaven.
İşte geliyor, Toretto'nun garajlndan yeni çlkmlş.
That was an $80,000 vehicle, Officer.
O araba 80.000 dolar değerindeydi memur bey.
- You told him what happened? - He knows.
- Ne olduğunu söyledin mi ona? - Biliyor.
- Send the bill to Johnny Tran. - The kid's giving me attitude?
- Faturayl Johnny Tran'a gönder. - Bu çocuğun bana garezi mi var?
Lt doesn't speak well for police/FBl relations, Tanner.
Polis-FBl ilişkisi açlslndan pek iyi değil bu Tanner.
- L walk in the door and the guy's already... - All right, all right.
- İçeriye girdiğimde herif çoktan... - Tamam, tamam.
We'll talk, okay? Let's talk about it.
Konuşallm, olur mu? Bu konuda konuşallm.
Muse, why don't you make us four iced cappuccinos, please?
Muse, bize dört tane buzlu kapuçino yapar mlsln lütfen?
- Come on. - Regular or decaf, Sarge?
- Haydi. - Normal mi, kafeinsiz mi komiser?
Decaf, l think.
Kafeinsiz sanlrlm.
BlLKlNS: Four hijackings in two months, and we have nothing.
İki ayda dört hlrslzllk oldu ve elimizde bir şey yok.
The DVD players and digital cameras are worth $1 .2 million
DVD göstericiler ve dijital kameralar 1,2 milyon değerinde.
which brings the grand total to $6 million plus.
Hepsi toplam altl milyon küsur tutuyor.
We're in the political crosshairs now, Brian.
Politikacllarln merceği altlndaylz Brian.
That's why you're undercover.
O yüzden gizli görevdesin.
BlLKlNS: You want that detective badge fast, kid. And you want to know something?
Dedektif rozetine hemen kavuşmak istiyorsun. Bir şey bilmek ister misin?
The FBl can help, if you come through for us.
Eğer bu işi klvlrlrsan FBl da sana yardlm eder.
What does the truck driver say?
Kamyoncu ne diyor?
He gave us the same M.O.: Three Honda Civics, precision driving,
Yöntem aynl: Üç adet Honda Civic, usta şoförler,
the same green neon glow from under the chassis.
şasinin altlnda aynl yeşil neon IşIğI.
Lab says the skidmarks came back the same: Mashamoto ZX tires.
Laboratuvar, lastik izlerinin aynl olduğunu söylüyor: Mashamoto ZX lastikleri.
So, we know it's somebody in the street-racing world.
Yani bunu bazl sokak yarlşçllarlnln yaptlğI kesin.
Lf we don't make this case, the truckers will take matters into their own hands.
Eğer bu olayl biz çözmezsek, kamyoncular işi kendileri halletmeye kalkar.
L tell them we're close.
Onlara sonuca yaklaştlğlmlzl söyledim.
Are you going to make me a liar?
Beni yalancl ml çlkarmak istiyorsun?
Look, what do we know?
Ne biliyoruz?
We know this world revolves around Toretto, right?
Bu dünya Toretto'nun etraflnda dönüyor, değil mi?
L'm not saying that he's the one that's popping these trucks,
Bu kamyonlarl soyan odur demiyorum,
but l can guarantee he knows who is. Lt's just a matter of time until l win...
ama kim olduğunu bildiğini garanti ederim. Sadece zaman lazlm, şeyi kazanana kadar...
You want time, buy the magazine. We don't have time.
Zaman ml lazlm, git Zaman gazetesini al. Ama bizim zamanlmlz yok.
Just get me something l can use.
Kullanabileceğim bir şey getir bana.
Ls Harry cooperating?
Harry işbirliği yaplyor mu?
Like a guy that'll do time for receiving stolen property if he doesn't.
Yapmazsa çallntl mal alan bir adam olarak hapse gireceğini biliyor.
What kind of vibe is he getting from Toretto?
Toretto hakklnda ne düşünüyor?
He's scared of him, but he doesn't think he's jacking trucks.
Ondan korkuyor, ama kamyonlarl onun soyduğunu düşünmüyor.
- He's too controlled for that. - Wait.
- Bunun için fazla kontrollü. - Bir dakika.
Not that l want to contradict Harry's fine judge of character,
Harry'nin yaptlğI bu kişilik tahlilini eleştirmek istemem,
but Toretto did hard time for nearly beating a guy to death.
ama Toretto'nun bir adaml öldüresiye dövmekten sablkasl var.
He's got nitrous oxide in his blood and a gas tank for a brain.
Kanlnda nitrojen var, beyin yerine benzin deposu taşlyor.
Do not turn your back on him.
Ona arkanl dönme sakln.
Tanner, l'm gonna need another car.
Tanner, başka bir arabaya ihtiyaclm var.
- What about parts and service? - Hold off on it.
- Parçalar ve servis ne olacak? - Sonra bakarlz.
Dom, l don't know what to do with it.
Dom, bu işi nasll halledeceğimi bilmiyorum.
All right, what the hell is this? What do you got there?
Pekala, nedir bu? Nereden buldun bunu?
- This is your car. - My car?
- Bu senin araban. - Benim arabam ml?
L said a 1 0-second car, not a 1 0-minute car.
1 0 saniyede maksimuma çlksln dedim, 1 0 dakikada değil.
You could push this across the finish line, or tow it.
Bitiş çizgisine kadar itmek gerekir bunu, ya da çekici kullanmak lazlm.
You couldn't even tow that across the finish line.
Bitiş çizgisine kadar çekiciyle bile gitmez bu.
No faith.
Hiç inancln yok.
L have faith in you, but this isn't a junkyard.
Sana inanlyorum, ama burasl araba mezarllğI değil.
- This is a garage. - Pop the hood.
- Burasl bir garaj. - Kaportayl aç.
- Pop the hood?
- Kaportayl ml?
- 2JZ engine. No shit. - And what did l tell you?
- 2JZ motor. Şakasl yok. - Ben sana ne dedim?
- L retract my previous statement. - You know what?
- Sözümü geri allyorum. - Biliyor musun?
This will decimate all after you put about $1 5,000 in it.
Sen 1 5.000 dolar harcadlktan sonra bu tam bir canavar olacak.
Or more, if we have to overnight parts from Japan.
Japonya'dan parçalarl uçakla gönderirlerse, 1 5.000'den fazla tutar.
- We'll put it on my tab at Harry's. - Yes!
- Harry hepsini hesablma yazar artlk. - Evet!
L gotta get you racing again so l can make some money off your ass.
Seni tekrar yarlştlraylm ki, slrtlndan biraz para kazanaylm.
There's a showdown in the desert called Race Wars.
Çölde Yarlş Savaşlarl diye bir gösteri var.
That's where you'll do it.
Orada yarlşacaksln.
When you're not working at Harry's, you're working here.
Harry'de çallşmadlğln zamanlar burada çallşacaksln.
Lf you can't find the right tool in this garage, Mr. Arizona,
Bu garajda doğru aleti bulamazsan Bay Arizona,
you don't belong near a car.
arabadan hiç anlamlyorsun demektir.
He owns you now.
Artlk senin sahibin oldu.
Tell me what you think about this. Koni adjustables.
Bu konuda ne düşündüğünü söyle bana. Koni ayarlanabilir amortisörler.
Gonna save us about 2 pounds.
Böylece bir kilo tasarruf etmiş olacağlz.
And they're gonna give us better traction for the hole shot.
Kalklşta iyi çekiş gücü sağlayacaklar.
All right?
Tamam ml?
This is your basic layout of the car.
Bu, arabanln kaba bir planl.
And that's pretty much what it could look like when it's finished.
Bittiğinde aşağI yukarl buna benzeyecek.
Red, green.
Kirmlzl, yeşil.
- You should be going to MlT or something. - Yeah, right.
- Senin MlT'de falan okuyor olman lazlmdl. - Evet, doğru.
No, l got that... What's it called?
Haylr, bende şey var... Ne deniyor ona?
That attention disorder...
Dikkat bozukluğu...
- ADD? - Yes, that shit. Yeah.
- Dikkatini toplayamama hastallğI ml? - Evet, her ne boksa ondan.
You know, l was good in algebra and like math and shit.
Cebir derslerim çok iyiydi, matematiği falan da severdim.
Everything else l failed. Dropped out of school.
Diğer derslerin hepsinden kaldlm. Okulu blraktlm.
L don't know. There's just something about engines
Bilmiyorum. Motorlarla ilgili şeyler
that calms me down, you know.
beni rahatlatlyor.
- L'm outta here. - Come on, dog.
- Ben gelmiyorum. - Yapma evlat.
- Yo, Dom. - Vince, get over here and give us a hand.
- Merhaba Dom. - Vince, buraya gel de bize yardlm et.
Looks like you got all the help you need, brother.
İhtiyacln olan bütün yardlml almlşsln zaten.
- Mia! The chicken's dry. - MlA: All right. l'm coming out already.
- Mia! Tavuk kurumuş. - Tamam. Geliyorum.
Here you go.
Al bakallm.
Wait, hold up.
Hey, dur bir dakika.
Because you were the first to reach in to get the chicken, you say grace.
Tavuğa ilk elini uzatan sen olduğun için dua edeceksin.
- Dear heavenly... - Spirit.
- Yüce... - Kutsal ruh.
Spirit. Thank you.
Kutsal ruh. Sağol ahbap.
Thank you for providing us with a direct port nitrous injection,
Bize verdiğin bu nimetler için, direkt nitrojen enjeksiyonu,
four core intercoolers and ball-bearing turbos
dört soğutuculu ve rulmanll turbo motorlar
and titanium valve springs.
ve titanyum supap yaylarl için sana şükrediyoruz.
- Thank you. - Amen.
- Şükürler olsun. - Amin.
- Not bad.
- Fena değil.
He was praying to the car gods, man.
Araba tanrllarlna dua ediyordu dostum.
He's not the best.
En iyisi değil.
- MlA: What do you want? - Practice.
- Nesi eksik? - Pratiği yok.
Thank you, girl.
Teşekkür ederim canlm.
Look who it is. "Old Coyotes 'R' Us."
Bak kim geliyor. Bizim küçük aylclk.
l thought you weren't hungry, pumpkin.
Aç olmadlğlnl sanlyordum balkabağlm.
- You know, l gotta eat. - He's always hungry.
- Benim de yemem gerek. - O her zaman açtlr.
All right, sit down.
Otur bakallm.
How you doing, Mia?
Nasllsln Mia?
Here you go.
Buyurun.
- Jesse, hand me that chicken. - Let's eat some grub, man.
- Jesse, o tavuğu bana ver. - Biraz tlklnallm dostum.
- Want some of that chicken? - What, you rent a movie or something?
- Biraz tavuk ister misin? - Film falan kiraladlnlz ml?
Need a hand with anything else?
Yardlma ihtiyacln var ml?
No, l'm good. You can go join the boys and watch the movie.
Haylr, idare ederim. Çocuklara katlllp film seyredebilirsin.
- The cook doesn't clean where l come from. - L'd like to go there.
- Bizim oralarda aşçllar bulaşlk ylkamaz. - Oraya gitmek isterdim.
- L think we should go out sometime. - No, l don't date my brother's friends.
- Bence bir akşam çlkmallylz. - Haylr, ağabeyimin arkadaşlarlyla çlkmam.
That sucks.
Çok saçma.
- L'll have to kick his ass then. - L'd love to see that one.
- O zaman onun klçlna tekmeyi basmallylm. - Bunu görmek isterim.
L would pay to see that one, actually.
Bunu görmek için para bile verebilirim.
Wash my car when you get done.
İşin bitince arabaml da ylka.
- What was that? - No, Mia. l'm talking to the punk.
- Ne dedin? - Sana değil Mia, bu küçük ibneye söyledim.
Wear your favorite dress, 'cause when you're done,
En güzel elbiselerini giy, çünkü işin bitince
l'm putting you on the street where you belong, cutie.
seni ait olduğun yere, sokağa blrakacağlm tatll çocuk.
Ls this thing broken? What's wrong with this thing?
Bu şey bozuk mu? Neyi var bunun?
What was that Cuban restaurant you wanted to take me to?
Beni götürmek istediğin o Küba restoranl neresiydi?
The one with the picadillo and...
Şu picadillo yapan yer...
- With red candles, wooden tables... - The plantain, food all over the place.
- Kirmlzl mumlarl, tahta masalarl olan... - Muz tatllsl var, ne ararsan var.
- What it's called? - Cha Cha Cha.
- Adl neydi? - Cha Cha Cha.
- Yeah, that's it. - Yeah.
- Evet, işte orasl. - Evet.
Well, you can take me there.
Beni oraya götürebilirsin.
Friday night at 1 0:00. Ls that good for you?
Cuma gecesi saat 1 0'da. Sana uyar ml?
- Yeah, it's perfect. - Good.
- Evet, kesinlikle. - İyi.
- There's no popcorn. - Make your own goddamn popcorn!
- Patlamlş mlslr nerede? - Git de patlamlş mlslrlnl kendin yap!
All right. Now that's valet parking.
Tamam. Böyle güzel park edilir işte.
- Harry. What's up, dog? - Nice to see you.
- Harry. Ne haber? - Seni görmek ne güzel.
Excellent. Come on in, man.
Harika. İçeri gir dostum.
- Check it. lt's yours. - Damn. What do we got here?
- Şuna bak. O senin. - Vay be. Neler var burada?
- Hired some new help? - Don't even think about it.
- Yeni yardlmcl ml tuttun? - Akllndan bile geçirme.
- What's up? - What's up, Brian? How you feeling?
- Ne haber? - Ne haber Brian? Nasllsln?
- Pretty good. What do you need? - What's up, man?
- Gayet iyiyim. Ne istiyorsun? - Ne haber dostum?
L need you to hook me up. Three of everything. l made a list.
Eksiklerimi tamamlamanl istiyorum. Her şeyden üç tane. Bir liste yaptlm.
Why don't you look that over?
Listeye bir göz atlver.
- When do you need this stuff by? - Tomorrow, today, now.
- Bunlarl ne zamana istiyorsun? - Yarln, bugün, şimdi.
- Right. - White boys work fast, don't they?
- Tamam. - Beyaz çocuklar hlzll çallşlr, değil mi?
That's right.
Doğru.
- BRlAN: You said you need three of each? - Yeah, three of everything.
- Her birinden üç tane lazlm, değil mi? - Evet, her şeyden üç tane.
What do you think about that? Check this out.
Ne dersin? Şuna bir bak.
He moans like a cop.
Polis gibi inliyor.
Brian, this is one of those times you need to be clear about what you say.
Brian, şu anda söyleyeceğin her şey çok açlk olmall.
Nod if you understand me.
Beni anllyorsan başlnl salla.
Nod!
Başlnl salla!
Sit up.
Kalk.
Tell me what the hell you're doing down here.
Burada ne yaptlğlnl söyle bana.
Shit. What l'm doing?
Kahretsin. Ne mi yaplyorum?
Dom.
Dom.
L owe you a 1 0-second car.
1 0 saniyede maksimuma çlkan bir araba borçluyum sana.
And what this is about, this is about Race Wars.
Bu ne mi demek, bu Yarlş Savaşlarl demek.
L just went in there, and Hector is gonna be running
Demin içeri baktlm, Hector, Spoon marka motoru olan
three Honda Civics with Spoon engines.
üç Honda Civic yarlştlracak.
And on top of that, he just came into Harry's
Üstüne üstlük, Harry'nin yerine geldi bugün
and he ordered three T66 turbos, with NOS,
ve üç tane nitrojen oksitli T66 motor
and a MoTeC system exhaust.
ve MoTeC sistemli egzoz Ismarladl.
So, what are you saying?
Yani ne demeye çallşlyorsun?
You're gonna check everybody's shit out, one garage after another?
Herkesi kontrol mü edeceksin, teker teker bütün garajlarl?
Yeah.
Evet.
Because, Dom, you know l can't lose again.
Çünkü Dom, biliyorsun, bir kere daha kaybedemem.
He's a cop.
O polis.
He's a cop!
O polis!
You a cop?
Sen polis misin?
Let's go for a little ride.
Arabayla biraz gezelim.
Walk!
Yürü!
Okay. You stand watch.
Tamam. Sen gözcülük yap.
Yo, Dominic.
Hey, Dominic.
There's no engines.
Motorlarl yok.
What are they planning on racing with, hopes and dreams?
Neyle yarlşmayl planllyorlar, umutlar ve düşlerle mi?
L don't know, but they're sneaky as shit
Bilmiyorum, ama çok sinsiler
and they've got enough money to buy anything.
ve her şeyi satln alacak kadar paralarl var.
What?
Ne var?
We got a wolf pack.
Bir kurt sürüsü geliyor.
Lt's Johnny Tran, and he's coming your way really fast.
Bu Johnny Tran, büyük bir hızla size doğru geliyor.
All right, we got company. Spilner.
Tamam, misafirimiz var. Spilner!
Come on. Move!
Haydi. Kimllda!
Let me ask you a question, Ted.
Sana bir soru sorabilir miyim Ted?
- Do you see anything wrong here? - No.
- Burada yanllş bir şey görüyor musun? - Haylr.
- We got no engines, do we?
- Motor yok, değil mi? - Haylr, yok.
- Do we? - No.
- Var ml? - Yok.
A couple of Nissan SR20 motors will pull a premium
Birkaç Nissan SR20 motoru bayağI kar getirir.
- one week before Race Wars, huh? - Yeah, probably.
- Hem de Yarlş Savaşlarlndan bir hafta önce. - Muhtemelen.
You're a smart fence, Ted. Maybe too smart.
Zeki bir tüccarsln. Belki de biraz fazla zeki.
What are you feeling, Lance?
Nasll olsun Lance?
40-weight?
Normal mi?
50-weight?
Süper mi?
A 40-weight sounds nice.
Normal iyi olur.
Where are they, Ted?
Neredeler Ted?
- Where are they? - Enough!
- Neredeler? - Yeter!
- They're in a warehouse.
- Bir depodalar.
They're in a warehouse, man!
Bir depodalar dostum!
Ted.
Ted.
Kiss my shoes?
Ayakkabllarlml yalar mlsln?
Let's go get our engines.
Gidip motorlarlmlzl alallm.
My superiors are flying in from D.C., in two days.
Amirlerim iki gün içinde Washington'dan gelecek.
L want something to show.
Gösterecek bir şey istiyorum.
We've got a fence with a lube hose in his mouth,
Ağzl motor yağI dolu bir çallntl mal tüccarl,
automatic weapons, priors on every one of these Asian punks,
otomatik silahlar, hepsi sablkall bazl Asyall serseriler,
a garage full of DVD players and generally psychotic behavior.
DVD göstericilerle dolu bir garaj ve psikopat davranlşlar.
Tell me why we shouldn't move on Tran now and figure it out later?
Neden şimdi Tran'i yakalaylp gerisini sonra halletmiyoruz?
Because all we have is behavior.
Eldeki tek şey kötü davranlşlar.
Let me get hard evidence, because what we have now is just...
Sağlam deliller bulaylm, çünkü şu anda elimizde sadece...
BlLKlNS: What we have is probable cause.
Elimizde muhtemel suçlular var.
And truckers arming themselves for some good old-fashioned vigilante mayhem.
Kamyoncular eski moda bir intikam saldlrlsl için silahlanlyor.
- Tell us about Hector, Brian. - Latinos with spear guns. Give me a break.
- Bize Hector'dan bahset Brian. - Oyuncak tabancall Latinler. Boşver gitsin.
Hector's still working on the engines, but the tires don't match.
Hector hala motorlar üzerinde çallşlyor, ama lastikler uymuyor.
Will somebody give me a cigarette?
Biri bana bir sigara verebilir mi?
- Get him a cigarette. - Don't give him one.
- Ona bir sigara getir. - Ona sigara verme.
- L thought you quit. - L did. Just give me one.
- Biraktln sanlyordum. - Evet. Sadece bir tane ver.
- Get him a cigarette. - No!
- Ona bir sigara getir. - Haylr!
Tell me about Toretto.
Bana Toretto'dan bahset.
L told you, l think he's too controlled for this.
Sana söyledim, bunu yapmayacak kadar kontrollü.
Going suicidal on semi-trucks? No way. Maybe Vince. But he's too dumb to do it.
Kamyonlar için intihara kalklşmak ml? Asla. Vince olabilirdi. Ama o da çok aptal.
- L think the kid sister's blurring your vision. - What did you say?
- Bence küçük klz kardeş gözlerini kör etmiş. - Ne dedin?
L don't blame you. l'd get off on her surveillance photos, too.
Seni suçlamlyorum. Ben de onun fotoğraflarlna baklp orgazm olabilirim.
Knock it off!
Kes şunu!
What? Are you going native on me, Brian?
Ne? Bana sinirlenecek misin Brian?
Have you read Toretto's file lately?
Yaklnlarda Toretto'nun dosyaslnl okudun mu?
- Yeah. l memorized that file. - Read it again.
- Evet. O dosyayl ezberledim. - Tekrar oku.
No, better still, take a look at these.
Daha iyisi, şunlara bir bak.
Remember l told you about the guy he nearly beat to death?
Öldüresiye dövdüğü adaml hatlrllyor musun?
Toretto did this with a three-quarter-inch torque wrench.
Toretto bunu iki santim kallnllğlnda bir ingilizanahtarlyla yapmlş.
He's a model of self-control.
Kesinlikle çok kontrollü bir adam.
L need a few more days.
Birkaç güne daha ihtiyaclm var.
Got a TR7 here, with a ball-bearing upgrade.
Güçlendirilmiş bir TR7 var elimizde.
What it's going to do is, it's going to spool up really quick.
Motorun devri çok artacak.
- L got this set up for 24 psi. - Got it.
- Bunu 24 psi olarak ayarladlm. - Anladlm.
You got big plans tonight?
Bu gece için önemli planlarln ml var?
Yeah. We're going out to dinner.
Evet. Yemeğe çlklyoruz.
You break her heart, l'll break your neck.
Onun kalbini klrarsan ben de senin boynunu klrarlm.
That's not gonna happen.
Bu hiç olmayacak.
L want to show you something.
Sana bir şey göstermek istiyorum.
Me and my dad built her.
Babamla birlikte yaptlk bunu.
Nine hundred horses of Detroit muscle.
900 beygir gücünde bir Detroit mucizesi.
Lt's a beast.
Tam bir canavar.
- You know what she ran in Palmdale? - No. What?
- Palmdale'de kaç yaptl biliyor musun? - Haylr. Kaç?
Nine seconds flat.
Tam dokuz saniye.
- God. - My dad was driving.
- Tanrlm. - Babam sürüyordu.
So much torque, the chassis twisted coming off the line.
Motorun devri o kadar fazlaydl ki çizgiyi geçerken şasi eğrilmişti.
Barely kept her on the track.
Onu zar zor yolda tutabildi.
- So, what's your best time? - L've never driven her.
- Senin en iyi zamanln nedir? - Ben onu hiç kullanmadlm.
Why not?
Neden?
Lt scares the shit out of me.
Beni çok korkutuyor.
That's my dad.
Babam.
He was coming up in the pro stock-car circuit.
Babam profesyonel yarlşta önde gidiyordu.
Last race of the season.
Sezonun en son yarlşI.
A guy named Kenny Linder came up from inside, in the final turn.
Kenny Linder adlnda bir adam son turda içeriden gelip yetişti.
He clipped his bumper and put him into the wall at 1 20.
Tamponuna çarptl ve onu 1 90 kilometre süratle duvara flrlattl.
L watched my dad burn to death.
Babamln yanarak ölüşünü seyrettim.
L remembered hearing him scream.
ÇIğllk attlğlnl duymuştum.
But the people that were there said he had died before the tanks blew.
Ama herkes benzin deposu alev almadan öldüğünü söyledi.
They said it was me who was screaming.
ÇIğllk atanln ben olduğumu söylediler.
L saw Linder about a week later.
Bir hafta kadar sonra Linder'a rastladlm.
L had a wrench, and l hit him.
Elimdeki ingiliz anahtarlyla ona vurdum.
And l didn't intend to keep hitting him, but when l finished, l couldn't lift my arm.
Ona vurmayl sürdürmek niyetinde değildim, ama işim bittiğinde, kolumu kaldlramadlm.
He's a janitor at a high school.
Bir lisede kaplclllk yaplyor.
He has to take the bus to work every day.
Her gün işine otobüsle gidiyor.
And they banned me from the tracks for life.
Ve bana ömür boyu pistleri yasakladllar.
L live my life a quarter mile at a time.
Hayatlml rölantide yaşlyorum.
Nothing else matters. Not the mortgage, not the store,
Hiçbir şeyin önemi yok. Ne ipoteğin, ne dükkanln,
not my team and all their bullshit.
ne de ekibimin.
For those 1 0 seconds or less,
1 0 saniyelik ya da daha hlzll arabalar için
l'm free.
her zaman müsaitim.
BRlAN: So, how is it, anyways, that the gang came to be?
Çete nasll oluştu peki?
MlA: What? BRlAN: The gang.
- Ne? - Çete.
MlA: The gang? No, they don't call themselves a gang.
Çete mi? Haylr, onlar kendilerine çete demiyor.
BRlAN: What do they call themselves? MlA: They're a team.
- Kendilerine ne diyorlar? - Onlar bir ekip.
- They call themselves a team. - All right. How did the team come to be?
- Kendilerine ekip diyorlar. - Pekala. Bu ekip nasll oluştu?
Well, that's a whole lot of history.
Şey, bu çok uzun bir hikaye.
- L've got time. - Okay. Vince grew up with my brother.
- Zamanlm var. - Tamam. Vince, ağabeyimle büyüdü.
Actually, he didn't ever actually grow up, as you can tell.
Asllnda pek büyümüş sayllmaz, senin de gördüğün gibi.
But they were friends as kids.
Ama çocukken arkadaştllar.
And Letty, she just lived down the street.
Letty de sokağln sonunda oturuyordu.
Always into cars, though. Ever since she was, like, 1 0 years old.
Ama arabalara karşI bir tutkusu vardl. On yaşlndan beri.
So, naturally, you know, my brother always had her attention.
Bu yüzden, ağabeyim her zaman onun ilgisini çekmiştir.
- And then she turned 1 6... - And then she had Dom's attention.
- Sonra 1 6 yaşlna girdi... - O da Dom'un ilgisini çekmeye başladl.
Yeah. lt's funny how that works, isn't it?
Evet. İşlerin böyle gelişmesi komik, değil mi?
Yeah.
Evet.
How does Jesse fit into the whole thing?
Peki Jesse aralarlna nasll katlldl?
Jesse. Well, Jesse and Leon just sort of showed up one night and never, ever left.
Jesse. Jesse ve Leon bir gece çlkageldiler ve bir daha hiç gitmediler.
Lt's just the way my brother is, you know. Dom's like...
Ağabeyim böyledir. Dom şey gibidir...
He's like gravity.
Yerçekimi gibidir.
Everything just gets pulled to him.
Her şey ona doğru çekilir.
Even you.
Sen bile.
No.
Haylr.
The only thing that pulled me in was you.
Beni çeken tek şey sendin.
Being friends with your brother is just a bonus.
Ağabeyinle arkadaş olmak işin ikramiyesi gibi.
That's good.
Bu iyi.
That's good. lt's nice to come first every once in a while.
Bazen ondan önce gelmek hoş oluyor.
Want to go for a drive?
Arabayla bir tur atmak ister misin?
- Yeah? - The hijackers have hit again.
- Efendim? - Hırsızlar tekrar atağa geçti.
Bilkins has decided that we're gonna move on Johnny Tran and his guys at 17:00.
Bilkins, saat 17.00'de Johnny Tran ve adamlarına baskın yapılmasına karar verdi.
Unless you say otherwise.
Sen başka bir şey demiyorsan.
Lf you agree, just say yes.
Onaylıyorsan, evet de.
- Yeah. - Who is that?
- Evet. - Kimdi o?
Lt's just a wrong number.
Yanllş numara.
BlLKlNS: Yes, sir. Yeah, l know, but...
Peki efendim. Evet, biliyorum, ama...
Yeah. Yes, sir.
Evet. Peki efendim.
Yeah. l got it.
Evet. Anladlm.
The DVD players were purchased legally.
DVD'ler yasal yoldan satln allnmlş.
All we've got are a couple of low-rent weapons charges
Elimizde olan, birkaç tane ruhsatslz silah bulundurma suçu
and some outstanding speeding tickets.
ve bir sürü aşlrl hlz cezasl.
- So, they're out. - Yeah.
- Yani serbestler. - Evet.
Father bailed them out.
Baba kefaletlerini ödemiş.
Ls this the kind of intelligence l can expect from you, O'Conner?
Senden beklediğim istihbarat bu muydu O'Conner?
- You're gonna put this on me? - L can put it on whoever l want to.
- Beni mi suçluyorsun? - Kimi istersem suçlarlm.
- Perks of the job. - No, you can't put this on me...
- Bu, işimin ikramiyesi. - Haylr, beni suçlayamazsln...
No, wait a minute. Let me tell you.
Haylr, bir dakika. Dinle beni.
L don't care if you have to aim at someone and blow your cover to smithereens.
Kimliğinin açIğa çlkmasl artlk umurumda değil. Birinin kafaslna silah daya istersen.
You've got 36 hours to crack this bastard
Bu piçi yakalamak için 36 saatin var,
or you might want to think about another career.
yoksa kendine başka bir meslek seçebilirsin.
Lt's Toretto, Brian. Lt always has been Toretto.
Bunu yapan Toretto. Başlndan beri Toretto'ydu.
Tran and Hector are...
Tran ve Hector...
They're just fumes.
Onlar slrf kuru gürültü.
L know you've been lying to me. My question is this:
Bana yalan söylediğini biliyorum. Sorum şu:
Have you been lying to yourself because you can't see past Mia?
Mia'yl kaybetmek istemediğin için kendine de mi yalan söylüyorsun?
He won't go back to prison.
Hapse geri dönmez.
Well, that's a choice he's going to have to make.
Bu onun yapmak zorunda kalacağI bir seçim.
There's all kinds of family, Brian.
Çeşit çeşit aile vardlr Brian.
And that's a choice you're gonna have to make.
Bu da senin yapmak zorunda olduğun bir seçim.
You ready for this?
Buna hazlr mlsln?
Nice car. What's the retail on one of those?
Güzel araba. Fiyatl ne kadar?
More than you can afford, pal. Ferrari.
Senin ödeyebileceğinden çok fazla oğlum. Ferrari bu.
Smoke him.
Göster şuna.
So, what's wrong, Brian?
Neyin var Brian?
Nothing, man, l'm fine.
Bir şey yok dostum, iyiyim.
Come on. Obviously something's off.
Haydi. Ters bir şey olduğu açlk.
Look, l have my good days and bad days just like anybody else.
Bak, benim de herkes gibi iyi ve kötü günlerim var.
Brian, don't lose that cool of yours. That's your meal ticket.
Brian, sinirlerine hakim ol. Ekmek paran bu senin.
My meal ticket? L can't pay for my own shrimp?
Ekmek param ml? Kendi karidesimin paraslnl ödeyemez miyim?
L got the shrimp.
Karidesi ben aldlm.
No, that's one thing about me you don't understand.
Haylr, beni iyi tanlmamlşsln.
L don't take handouts. L earn my way, every step.
Sadaka almam. Hayatlml kendim kazanlrlm.
L need something extra on the side, like you.
Senin gibi ek bir kazanç kaplsl istiyorum.
What do you mean, like me?
Ne demek benim gibi?
- What's that supposed to mean? - That's what l mean.
- Bu ne demek oluyor şimdi? - Demek istediğimi anladln.
- What does that mean, like me? - Don't try...
- Ne demek benim gibi? - Sakln deneme...
l'm not stupid, all right?
Ben aptal değilim, tamam ml?
L know that there's no way you paid for all that shit you got under the hood...
Kaportanln altlndaki o parçalarln paraslnl ödeyebilmen mümkün değil.
There's no way you paid for what's under the hood of those cars
O arabalarln parçalarlnln paraslnl
by doing tune-ups and selling groceries.
tamir yaplp sandviç satarak ödemene imkan yok.
Whatever it is you're in on, l want in on it, too.
Çevirdiğin işler her neyse, ben de dahil olmak istiyorum.
- Well, what is this? - Read it.
- Bu da ne? - Oku.
- What is this for? - Lt's directions.
- Ne için bu? - Talimatlar.
To Race Wars.
Yarlş Savaşlarl için.
We'll see how you go.
Bakallm ne yapacaksln.
Then we'll talk.
O zaman konuşuruz.
- BRlAN: How's it going? - What's up?
- Nasll gidiyor? - Ne haber?
- Welcome to Race Wars. - Great. Thanks a lot.
- Yarlş Savaşlarlna hoşgeldin. - Harika. Çok sağol.
Baby. Hey, baby.
Bebek. Selam bebek.
You should watch from the side.
Kenardan izlemelisin.
L wouldn't want to get exhaust on that pretty face.
O güzel yüzün egzoz dumanl olmaslnl istemem.
- Put your money where your mouth is. - L'll race you for that sweet little ass.
- Paranl ağzlna sok. - O güzel klçln için yarlşacağlm seninle.
You want ass, why don't you hit Hollywood Boulevard?
KIç peşindeysen, Hollywood Bulvarlna git.
You want an adrenaline rush, it'll be two large.
Ama damarlarlnda adrenalin istiyorsan, iki yüz dolara patlar.
Right here. Right now. What's it gonna be?
Hemen burada. Hemen şimdi. Ne dersin?
You got it.
Anlaştlk.
"Another one bites the dust"
"Bu da yuttu tozumu."
Come on. What you got?
Haydi. Neyin var?
See ya.
Görüşürüz.
- What's up? - Hey, what's up, Jesse?
- Ne haber? - Selam, ne haber Jesse?
What's in your hand?
Elinde ne var?
Throwing down the pink slip, just like you.
Tipkl senin gibi arabaml koyuyorum ortaya.
- The pink slip to what? The Jetta? - Yeah.
- Hangi arabayl? Jetta'yl ml? - Evet.
- You can't bet your dad's car. - Lt's all right.
- Babanln arabaslyla bahse giremezsin. - Dert değil.
L ain't losing.
Kaybetmeyeceğim.
This fool is running a Honda 2000. L'll win.
Bu salak, Honda 2000 kullanlyor. Ben kazanacağlm.
That way, me and my dad can roll when he gets out of prison. lt's all good.
Böylece babam hapisten çlktlktan sonra birlikte dolaşabiliriz. Her şey yolunda.
They're gonna throw him right back in prison after he kills you.
Baban seni öldürünce onu kodese geri gönderirler.
VlNCE: You visualize the win.
Kazanacağlnl hayal et.
Visualize the win, Jesse. l'm serious. You got to listen to me, man.
Hayal et Jesse. Ciddiyim. Beni dinle dostum.
Who are you racing?
Kiminle yarlşlyorsun?
Jesse, don't do it.
Jesse, yapma bunu.
L bet you he's got more than $1 00,000 under the hood of that car.
İddiaya girerim, o kaportanln altlndakiler 1 00.000 dolar eder.
Too soon, junior.
Fazla erken acemi.
No!
Haylr!
Shit!
Kahretsin!
Oh, God!
Aman tanrlm!
Yo! Heads up, bro. We got problems.
Hey! Dinle. Başlmlz dertte.
- What? - Jesse.
- Ne var? - Jesse.
Where's Jesse going?
Jesse nereye gidiyor?
- He just raced Tran for slips. - Oh, shit.
- Demin arabayl ortaya koyup Tran'la yarlştl. - Kahretsin.
- Where's he going? - He went to the car wash.
- Nereye gidiyor? - Arabayl ylkatmaya gitti.
Whatever. Go fetch my car.
Her neyse. Git arabaml getir.
Go fetch your car?
Senin arabanl ml getireyim?
We're not on your block.
Biz senin uşağln değiliz.
You better watch who you talk to like that.
Kiminle konuştuğuna dikkat etsen iyi olur.
Toretto!
Toretto!
SWAT came into my house,
Özel tim evime girdi,
disrespected my whole family, because somebody narked me out.
bütün ailemin şerefiyle oynadl, çünkü biri beni gammazlamlştl.
And you know what? lt was you!
Biliyor musun? O sendin!
VlNCE: Get off of him, man.
Birak onu dostum.
Dom, chill out, man. Come on!
Dom, sakin ol dostum. Haydi!
L never narked on nobody!
Ben kimseyi gammazlamadlm!
MlA: l have respected you and l haven't said shit.
Sana saygl gösterdim ve hiçbir şey söylemedim.
Now l am asking you not to go.
Şimdi gitmemeni rica ediyorum.
L'm doing this for both of us. MlA: Don't give me that crap.
- Bunu ikimiz için yaplyorum. - Bana maval okuma.
You're doing this for you.
Kendin için yaplyorsun.
Why are you insisting on doing this? Dom, please, just don't.
Neden bunu yapmakta Israr ediyorsun? Dom, lütfen yapma.
- BRlAN: Mia, what's going on? - What?
- Mia, neler oluyor? - Ne?
- You know what l'm talking about. - No, l don't.
- Neden bahsettiğimi biliyorsun. - Bilmiyorum.
You always have tears in your eyes when Dom drives away?
Ne zaman Dom arabaslna binip gitse senin gözlerin doluyor.
What's the matter with you?
Neyin var senin?
What's he racing off in the middle of the night for?
Gece vakti telaşla nereye gidiyor böyle?
- You know about the trucks? - No, Brian! What trucks?
- Kamyonlardan haberin var ml? - Haylr Brian! Ne kamyonu?
- Jesus Christ. What? - Listen to me.
- Of tanrlm. Ne var? - Beni dinle.
Mia, l'm a cop.
Mia, ben polisim.
What are you talking about, Brian? What is this?
Sen neden bahsediyorsun Brian? Neler oluyor?
Ever since the first time l met you, l've been undercover.
Seninle tanlştlğlm ilk günden beri gizli görevdeyim.
L'm a cop.
Ben polisim.
Oh, you bastard.
Seni piç.
You bastard.
Piç herif.
- Mia. - Get off of me, Brian!
- Mia. - Birak beni Brian!
Mia! Listen to me!
Mia! Dinle beni!
Everything l ever said l felt about you was real.
Sana olan duygularlm gerçek.
L swear to God. You have to believe me, Mia.
Yemin ederim. Bana inanmak zorundasln Mia.
But this isn't about you and me. Your brother's out there to pull a job.
Ama bu seninle benim meselem değil. Ağabeyin orada iş üzerinde.
We're running out of time. Those truckers aren't laying down anymore.
Zamanlmlz darallyor. O kamyoncular artlk buna izin vermez.
Maybe they'll make it through tonight, but every law enforcement agency
Belki de bu geceki işi becerirler, ama bütün polisler
is coming down on them.
onlarln peşinde.
Lf you don't want anything to happen to them,
Onlara bir şey olmaslnl istemiyorsan
you have to get in that car with me right now and help me.
hemen benimle şu arabaya binip bana yardlm etmek zorundasln.
Mia, you are the only person that can help me right now.
Mia, bana yardlm edebilecek tek insan sensin.
Please, Mia. Please help me.
Lütfen Mia. Lütfen bana yardlm et.
Civics are stashed somewhere outside of Thermal.
Hondalar termik santralin dlşlnda bir yere gizlenmiş.
They wouldn't double back, and Highway 1 0 is too well patrolled.
Aynl yolu iki defa kullanmazlar ve 1 0. Otoyolda çok devriye var.
- So, what does that leave us with? - All this.
- Geriye ne kallyor? - Bütün bu yollar.
- Nextel. - This is Officer Brian O'Conner.
- Nextel, buyurun. - Ben memur Brian O'Conner.
Serial number 34762. L need a cell phone trace.
Yaka numarasl 34762. Bir cep telefonunun izini bulmak istiyorum.
- Okay. What's the cell number? - Mia, what is it?
- Tamam. Numara nedir? - Mia, numara ne?
Come on, Mia. She needs Dom's cell phone number now.
Haydi Mia. Dom'un cep numaraslnl istiyor.
323-555-6439.
323-555-6439.
Thank you. Yeah, you get that?
Teşekkür ederim. Evet, aldlnlz ml?
All right, we're one man short. Letty, l need you on the left side.
Pekala, bir adam eksiğimiz var. Letty, sen sola geç.
Your sister's right about this one. This don't feel good.
Kiz kardeşin bu konuda hakll. Bu iş hoşuma gitmiyor.
- Don't do that. - Something's wrong.
- Bunu yapma. - Bir terslik var.
- Stop. - We shouldn't be doing this without Jesse.
- Dur. - Jesse olmadan bunu yapmamallylz.
This is the mother lode. We've been on this for three months.
Bu en büyük iş. Üç aydlr bunun üzerinde çallşlyoruz.
After this, it's a long vacation for everyone.
Bundan sonra hepimiz uzun bir tatile çlkacağlz.
- Let's go. - L hope so.
- Gidelim. - Umarlm.
Listen, the other night l had a dream
Dinle, geçen gece bir rüya gördüm.
that you and l were on the beach in Mexico.
Sen ve ben Meksika'daki kumsaldaydlk.
- Really? - Really.
- Gerçekten mi? - Gerçekten.
Come on. Let's make this happen.
Haydi. Rüyayl gerçek yapallm.
- Leon, keep on those scanners. - Copy that.
- Leon, o taraylcllardan gözünü aylrma. - Anlaşlldl.
All right, let's go.
Pekala, gidelim.
Okay, we traced the number to the northbound 86.
Numarayı 86. Otoyolda kuzey yönünde bulduk.
Mile 1 14, outside Coachella. We'll keep the trace open, Officer.
Coachella'nın 183 km dışında. İzlemeye devam ediyoruz memur bey.
Let me see this.
Şuna bakaylm.
L think we're about 40 miles away.
Sanlrlm 65 kilometre mesafedeyiz.
What are you gonna do?
Ne yapacaksln?
Okay! Go time!
Tamam! Başllyoruz!
We're all good. L got nothing on the scanners.
Başlamaya hazlrlz. Taraylcllarda bir şey yok.
Keep going.
Devam et.
Vince!
Vince!
Vince, don't! Get back in!
Vince, yapma! Geri dön!
He's got a damn shotgun! Leon!
Silahl var! Leon!
Back off! Get him off of there!
Geri çekil! Kamyondan al onu!
Oh, shit!
Kahretsin!
Get me off this thing! Pull up!
Buradan kurtar beni! Çek!
Unhook yourself. Do it!
Kurtar kendini. Haydi!
- Do it! - L can't get...
- Yap şunu! - Kurtulamlyorum...
You can do it!
Yapabilirsin!
Come on, Vince!
Haydi Vince!
Dom! l'm pulling up to distract him!
Dom! Dikkatini dağltmak için öne geçiyorum.
Come on, boy!
Haydi oğlum!
Shot doesn't get better than this.
Daha iyi nişan al.
Son of a bitch!
Orospu çocuğu!
Take me off here, or l'll have to unhook the wire!
Kurtar beni buradan, yoksa ipi salacağlm!
Try it again. One, two, three!
Tekrar dene. Bir, iki, üç!
Unhook yourself!
Kurtar kendini!
L can't get my arm free!
Kolumu kurtaramlyorum!
- Vince, grab my hand! - My arm!
- Vince, elimi tut! - Kolum!
Listen, give me your hand.
Dinle, elini ver bana.
L'm gonna pull you off the rig!
Seni çekeceğim!
Vince!
Vince!
Hold on!
Dur!
Give me your hand! Listen to me!
Elini ver bana! Dinle beni!
Dominic!
Dominic!
Shit!
Kahretsin!
- Dominic! - Hang on!
- Dominic! - Dayan!
Dom! Move out of the way. L'm coming to get him.
Dom! Yoldan çekil. Onu almaya geliyorum.
Letty!
Letty!
- Leon! - Yo!
Leon!
Pull back for Letty.
Letty'yi bul.
Get her out of there!
Onu arabadan çıkar!
L'm on it! Go!
Tamam! Sen devam et!
L've got her! You get Vince off that truck.
Onu buldum! Sen Vince'i kamyondan kurtar.
Letty! Come on, baby.
Letty! Haydi canlm.
You okay?
İyi misin?
Oh, shit. Come on, girl, you all right?
Kahretsin. Haydi canlm, iyi misin?
Come on, let me look at you. Come on. We got to go. Let's go.
Sana bakaylm. Haydi. Gitmek zorundaylz. Gidelim.
Vince!
Vince!
Take the wheel.
Direksiyona geç.
- What do you mean? - Put your foot on the gas!
- Ne demek istiyorsun? - Gaza bas!
L'm gonna get him. Put your foot on the gas!
Onu yakalayacağlm. Gaza bas!
MlA: Okay!
Tamam!
- BRlAN: Come on. Keep it steady. - L got it!
- Haydi. Devam et. - Tamam!
All right, hold on, Vince.
Pekala, dayan Vince.
He's having a hard time holding on. Get me a little closer.
Dayanamayacak. Biraz daha yaklna götür beni.
All right.
Tamam.
- Closer. - L'm moving in.
- Daha yaklna. - Yaklaşlyorum.
Hold it right there!
Böyle kal!
Go!
Şimdi!
You got to hang in here with me now!
Şimdi benimle buraya asllmallsln.
We'll get you off. Give me your arm!
Seni çekip alacağlz. Bana kolunu ver!
Vince, look at me! Don't let go!
Vince, bana bak! Birakma!
Come on, Vince! Throw this arm around me!
Haydi Vince! Kolunu boynuma dola!
Vince, don't let go!
Birakma Vince!
Come on, Mia. Get closer!
Haydi Mia. Biraz daha yaklaş!
Mia, get closer! Come on.
Mia, biraz daha yaklaş! Haydi.
Come on, Vince. Here we go!
Haydi Vince. Gidiyoruz.
BRlAN: Shit.
Kahretsin.
Lt's gonna be okay, Letty. l love you.
Her şey yoluna girecek Letty. Seni seviyorum.
- Watch her. - L got her.
- Ona dikkat et. - Merak etme.
Come on, Vince! Hang in there! Come on!
Haydi Vince! Dayan biraz! Haydi!
Lf he doesn't get to an ambulance in 1 0 minutes, he's dead.
On dakika içinde ambulans gelmezse ölür.
- Hold the pressure. Hold his arm up. - MlA: l got it.
- Tamponu tut. Kolunu kaldlr. - Tamam.
Yeah. Yeah, this is Officer Brian O'Conner.
Evet. Evet, ben memur Brian O'Conner.
L'm off-duty MAPD.
Minneola Emniyetinde memurum.
L need a life flight roll out right away.
Hemen bir hava ambulansl göndermenizi istiyorum.
My 20 is Highway 86, mile marker 147.
Pozisyonum, 86. Otoyol, 236. Kilometre taşI.
L got one trauma victim, about 24 years of age.
Travma geçiren bir yarall var, 24 yaşlarlnda.
Six-foot, maybe 200 pounds.
1 .80 boyunda, yaklaşlk 90 kilo ağlrllğlnda.
He's got a deep laceration to his right arm with arterial bleeding.
Sağ kolunda derin bir kesik ve atardamar kanamasl var.
And he's got a shotgun wound close range to his left flank.
Ve sol kaburgaslna yakln bir yerde bir kurşun yarasl var.
Yeah, he's going into shock!
Evet, şoka giriyor!
Dom, put the gun down now!
Dom, silahl yere at hemen!
- Move your car. - No bullshit!
- Çek arabanl. - Bir hata yapaylm deme!
Put it down now! No more running!
Onu yere at hemen! Artlk kaçamazsln!
L'm not running!
Kaçmlyorum!
- Where's Leon and Letty? - They're long gone!
- Leon'la Letty nerede? - Çoktan gittiler!
Then it's over. l didn't call the police, but don't push me!
Öyleyse her şey bitti. Polis çağlrmadlm, beni buna zorlama!
- Put the gun down. l swear to God! - You are the cop!
- Silahl yere at. Yemin ediyorum! - Polis sensin!
You're a cop!
Polis sensin!
Brian, l got to find Jesse before they do.
Onlar bulmadan Jesse'yi bulmam lazlm.
- L'm all the kid's got. - L'll call in the plates.
- Benden başka kimsesi yok. - Plakaslnl merkeze veririm.
PD will pick him up way before Johnny even gets near him.
Devriye ekibi Johnny'den önce bulur onu.
- Move your car. - Dom, stop it! lt's over. Please.
- Çek arabanl. - Dom, kes şunu! Her şey bitti. Lütfen.
Mia, stay out of it! Move the...
Mia, sen karlşma bu işe!
Dominic, l am so sorry.
Çok üzgünüm Dominic.
L don't know what l'm doing, Dom.
Ne yaptlğlml bilmiyorum Dom.
L'm so scared right now. L don't know what's going on.
Şu anda o kadar korkuyorum ki. Ne olacak bilmiyorum.
What were you thinking, man?
Ne düşünüyordun dostum?
L don't know! l panicked! l'm sorry.
Bilmem! Paniğe kaplldlm! Kusura bakma.
L'm scared!
Korkuyorum!
L don't know what l'm doing! Will you please help me?
Bunu nasll yaptlm bilmem! Lütfen bana yardlm eder misin?
Dom!
Dom!
No, Jesse!
Haylr Jesse!
No, Dom, no!
Haylr Dom, haylr!
Call 91 1 . You call 91 1!
Polis imdatl ara! Çabuk!
L used to drag here back in high school.
Lisedeyken burada yarlşlrdlm.
That railroad crossing up there is exactly a quarter mile away from here.
Şuradan geçen demiryolu sadece 400 metre uzakta.
On green, l'm going for it.
Yeşil yanlnca oraya gidiyorum.
That's not what l had in mind.
Benim akllmdaki bu değildi.
You know what you're doing?
Ne yaptlğlnl biliyor musun?
L owe you a 1 0-second car.
Sana 1 0 saniyede maksimuma çlkan bir araba borçluyum.
L live my life a quarter mile at a time.
Hayatımı rölantide yaşıyorum.
Nothing else matters.
Hiçbir şeyin önemi yok.
For those 10 seconds or less,
10 saniyelik ya da daha hızlı arabalar için
I'm free.
her zaman müsaitim.